Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I. Fok Chi-ho. solemnly. sincerely.
and truly declare and affirm
that the testimony I give
is based solely on the facts.
the whole truth.
and nothing but the truth.
Calling Central Control. Car 21.
We are in Kam Tin. requesting backup.
An EU vehicle is attacked.
We need an ambulance.
Around 15 male suspects here.
heavily armed. Requesting reinforcement.
On 27 July 2017.
I received an order from Central Control.
saying that one
of the EU vehicles was attacked.
And the attackers
were the gangsters we've been pursuing.
Open fire!
Three in front!
Suppress fire!
Go! Go!
Take cover!
Officer Lee. One front left.
Man down. Cover!
Ten in Zone B.
We're under heavy fire!
One fella is injured.
Cover Officer Fok.
Officer Fok. Cover me.
Go to hell!
Eight more in Zone B.
All round defense.
Hold on.
Officer Fok. Watch out above!
Stoppage! Guard!
Out of the way! Bomb!
As you saw.
what was the first defendant
doing at the scene?
I saw Officer Leung May-yee
chasing the first defendant.
Cheung Man-bing.
Don't run! Stop!
I saw the first defendant
escaping through the back door.
So. I chased him.
When you were chasing my client.
performing your duties.
did you carry your warrant card?
It was an emergency.
I dropped my warrant card.
So. you failed to establish
your identity as a police officer.
I certainly did not know
she was a police officer.
I heard gunshots. then a crazy woman
rushed up trying to attack me.
At that time. Officer Leung
was behind him. trying
to subdue the first defendant.
Cheung Man-bing.
In other words. my client
- was attacked by her from behind.
- I absolutely disagree.
He was forced to act in self-defense
and caused the accident.
Officer Leung
reasonably attempted
to subdue the first defendant.
Cheung Man-bing.
Cheung Man-bing intended to resist arrest.
Go to hell.
The prosecution points out
that you were unreasonably
at a deserted ruin.
How do you explain it?
I wanted to film something supernatural
for my YouTube channel.
We didn't find any photographic
equipment at the crime scene.
The defendant is giving a false testimony
and is in flagrant contempt of court.
Nowadays. a mobile phone
can film many things.
The prosecution's accusations
are unreasonable.
Ten gangsters were arrested.
All of them denied knowing my client.
It is sufficient to prove
that my client is not related
to this case at all.
Who will testify against their own boss?
Are you kidding me?
Silence.
Your Honor.
They are likely to collude and lie.
Their testimonies are unreliable.
The fact is that after
the police's forensic search.
the scene and weapons
contained no fingerprints
or DNA of my client.
The prosecution has made
accusations against my client
without any evidence or witnesses.
which are deemed as defamation.
I must remind the jury
that even if you suspect my client's
presence was unreasonable.
the benefit of doubt
should go to the defendant.
I earnestly request that you
pronounce my client innocent
because it is the only reasonable verdict.
Your Honor. I request a reopening
of the prosecution's case
and the summoning of new witnesses.
On what basis?
You should know the law.
Since the prosecution is not able
to prove guilt beyond a reasonable doubt.
and the jury reached a majority verdict.
I hereby declare
that the defendant. Cheung Man-bing.
is not guilty on all three charges.
possession of firearms.
assaulting a police officer.
and resisting arrest.
and be released by the court.
Law enforcement is just
the beginning of the legal process.
When there are any small cracks.
we lose justice.
Get off.
Move.
Let's go.
Officer Fok.
All the best.
Just a change of scenery.
Stick to your post.
Stick to our post.
AFTER A JEWELRY STORE ROBBERY
A HEROIC COP CAUGHT THREE ROBBERS
SEVEN YEARS LATER
The female defendant
stabbed the victim over 20 times.
Most of the stabs hit bone.
How will you deal with it?
She murdered him.
then remained at the crime scene.
She admitted she wanted
to kill the victim for a long time.
The evidence is conclusive.
Charge her with murder.
However. we need to consider
the crime scene was the victim's home.
The female defendant picked up
the fruit knife by chance.
It was not premeditated.
Charging her with murder might not work.
No fingerprints were found in the house.
She intentionally cleaned up the scene.
then waited for the police to arrest her.
Don't you think that's strange?
Mr. Fok.
You are an experienced HK police officer
who transferred to assist us at the DOJ.
You must have some insights.
Just a career move.
Let's investigate together.
I have another viewpoint.
Most of the fatal injuries
were on the left side.
Like this…
But the suspect is left-handed.
She would have had to use
a backhand. like this.
It is not impossible.
but it would be difficult.
Keep in mind.
the victim was a 200-pound man.
stronger than Benny.
- Benny.
- Yes.
Please help me to demonstrate.
- Maggie. right?
- Yes. Hello.
First. try to struggle with each other.
- Try to stab Benny. Maggie.
- Okay!
- Come on!
- Here I come.
- Come on.
- More force.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Hey!
Thank you…
So. as you can see.
a slim woman.
weighing around 90 pounds.
found it difficult to stab a 200-pound man
who worked out regularly.
like this.
In other words.
the murderer is likely someone else.
It's my opinion.
We have different opinions.
How about we make a bet?
- $500 for each.
- Sure.
How about we bet beer instead?
If I lose. my treat.
- Okay.
- Sure.
If you win. our treat.
- Okay.
- Deal.
Mr. Fok.
Yes?
- My name is Bao Ding.
- Hello.
I'm the Pupil Master here.
I take care of all the newcomers.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'll assist you in the first few cases.
If you need anything. please let me know.
Police are responsible for arrests.
We. the DOJ.
are responsible for prosecuting
and convicting the arrested suspects.
This is your first case.
Earlier this year.
Customs received a tip-off.
It is said that someone send a parcel
to import
one kilograms of cocaine from Brazil.
So. the police ambushed
and traced it to the home
of the first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
They arrested him
when he received the parcel.
Coming.
- Are you Ma Ka-kit?
- Yes. I am.
Sign here.
FROM BRAZIL TO MA KA-KIT. HONG KONG
Police. This is my warrant card.
We suspect drugs in your parcel.
- Kit!
- Stop!
Don't run!
I've got nothing to do with this!
I don't know anything.
- Kit!
- There are drugs inside. sir.
This parcel isn't mine.
I only lent someone my address.
After being arrested. Ma Ka-kit insisted
that he only lent his address
to the second defendant. Chan Kwok-wing.
And the police actually found drugs
at Chan Kwok-wing's home.
I want a lawyer.
The culprit was caught red-handed.
There is no case.
However. after three months of remand.
Ma Ka-kit suddenly reversed his testimony.
claiming that he never lent
his address to Chan Kwok-wing.
- What do you think?
- Ma Ka-kit has no criminal record.
but his testimony is inconsistent.
That means he's lying.
Chan Kwok-wing
has a drug possession record.
and drugs were found at his home.
Let's charge both of them.
Both of them are suspects.
Let's see how the defense reacts.
If you are planning anything.
you need Prosecutor Yeung's approval.
That's the rule. Please follow it.
Understood. Thank you.
And about the beer bet…
It's good to be confident.
Mr. Bao…
I love beer.
You were caught red-handed in this case.
It's difficult to avoid conviction.
I suggest you plead guilty
because pleading guilty now
can reduce your sentence by one-third.
I just lent my address
to someone for $1.000.
I didn't know it's about drugs.
Do I have to go to jail?
Kit.
We all believe you are innocent.
but there's no evidence to prove
that Chan Kwok-wing used your address.
If we lose the trial.
we will appeal.
If we win.
the Department of Justice will appeal.
Each appeal requires scheduling.
which means you will wait
endlessly in prison.
Barrister Li's advice is the best
and the quickest way to get you out.
If Kit pleads guilty.
can we proceed to the trial immediately
without him going to prison?
Actually. there are still many procedures
and formalities before the trial.
and Chan Kwok-wing's lawyer
will also take action.
You're Chan Kwok-wing. right?
Now that the police
found drugs in your house
and Ma Ka-kit has implicated you.
saying that you used his address
to receive the parcel.
the DOJ may charge you with conspiracy
to drug trafficking and possession.
How can I work with you?
First. we need to convince the police
that Kit will change his plea to guilty.
The police will then hand over
the documents to the DOJ.
CONFESSION REPORT MA KA-KIT
The DOJ will propose
a court mention after review.
The court will schedule
the trial as soon as possible.
for Kit to appeal for leniency.
Due to the large number of cases
the court has to handle.
the later you decide to plead guilty.
the longer you will have to wait.
But if Kit pleads guilty earlier.
we can immediately schedule
the case in the High Court
for him to appear to seek leniency.
CONFESSION REPORT MA KA-KIT
Don't say I didn't remind you.
When you were a cop.
you worshipped Lord Guan.
Now you're in the DOJ.
you should worship Prosecutor Yeung.
Remember that.
Hello. Mr. Bao.
Hello. You are?
I am the lawyer representing
Ma Ka-kit. Li Sze-man.
Is it possible to discuss
a plea agreement?
The conditions?
My client will admit to drug trafficking.
The only condition is that
the prosecution must withdraw
the conspiracy to drug trafficking
charge against Chan Kwok-wing.
You are the lawyer for the first defendant
and you want to withdraw
the charge against the second defendant?
- This doesn't make sense.
- Ma Ka-kit changed
his testimony because he felt guilty.
stating that it has nothing to do
with Chan Kwok-wing.
He didn't want to wrong
an innocent person.
Chan Kwok-wing. the second defendant.
has a drug possession record.
while the first defendant
has a clear record.
It is fair to release the first defendant
but not the second defendant.
Conspiracy will result
in a more severe punishment.
Excluding conspiracy
with the second defendant
is in my client's best interest.
Sorry. I don't accept it.
Shirley.
- Prosecutor Yeung.
- Good morning.
Morning.
Plea bargaining is great.
The defendant recognized his mistake
and pleaded guilty.
saving us time and taxpayers' money.
- I agree.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Hello. Good morning.
- Mr. Yeung.
This is the new prosecutor. Fok Chi-ho.
- Hi. Mr. Fok.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
We will go through
the court procedures later…
And that will settle the case.
Thank you.
- Prosecutor Yeung.
- Yes?
Why not charge the second defendant?
It doesn't comply
with the Prosecution Code.
The first defendant's testimony
consistently emphasized
that the second defendant
is not related to the case.
- So. I don't want to waste time.
- A waste of time?
This is our duty. Prosecution.
trial.
finding the truth. and conviction.
The Department of Justice's principle
has always been
to charge with evidence
and to release if no evidence.
Firstly. if the first defendant
admits to drug trafficking.
we can charge the second defendant
with drug possession.
That means both individuals
who have committed a crime
will go to prison.
What more do you want?
Your case involves
drug trafficking through mail.
So. strictly speaking.
whether others were involved
in drug trafficking is irrelevant to you.
As a prosecutor.
you should understand that.
It's almost ten o'clock.
Okay. Court.
Both of them plead guilty.
and both will be sentenced.
Isn't that fair? What more do you want?
Case number ESCC235/2023.
The first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
and the second defendant. Chan Kwok-wing.
are suspected
of conspiracy to drug trafficking.
Your Honor.
The defense has reached
an agreement with the prosecution.
My client. the first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
will admit to the charge
of drug trafficking.
Does the prosecution agree?
Your Honor.
the DOJ will amend the charge
against the first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
to drug trafficking and withdraw
the conspiracy to drug trafficking against
the second defendant. Chan Kwok-wing.
but we will retain the charge
of drug possession against him.
Ma Ka-kit.
you are accused of having
one kilogram of cocaine
mailed from overseas to your residence.
You were arrested on the scene
while receiving the parcel.
You are now charged with drug trafficking.
How do you plead?
I plead guilty.
Can I have remission?
Verdict will be made at the next hearing.
This judge pronounces
the withdrawal of the charge
of the second defendant.
Chan Kwok-wing. with
conspiracy to drug smuggling.
His drug possession case
will be scheduled for trial.
The first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
who admits to drug trafficking.
will be referred to the High Court
for mitigation and sentencing.
He will remain in custody.
- Court adjourned.
- Court.
Everyone wants to leave work early.
just like prisoners
want to be released early.
What's the problem?
No problem at all.
You are in charge of Ma Ka-kit's case.
You've interviewed him.
- What do you think?
- Initially. he resisted arrest.
but was very cooperative
later at the police station.
He kept saying it had
nothing to do with him
and that he only lent his address.
No criminal will admit guilt. right?
I heard he had
a tragic background. though.
How so?
It hurts! That's not how you do it!
You wasted everything!
Why can't you do anything right?
You're so useless.
- Please stop…
- Why can't you learn?
When he was young.
his father died from a drug overdose.
Whenever his mother craved drugs.
she would beat him. He ended up
in the hospital every time.
Bastard!
Hey. don't…
Stop…
The most remarkable part is that
his grandpa repaid his mother in kind
and regained custody.
so he wouldn't be sent to an orphanage.
His mother deserved it.
Tell me about it!
Finally got you. bastard.
Hey.
You bastard. leave me alone.
Don't move!
I'm a cop.
You hear me?
Come and help.
My bro.
Are you causing trouble here?
You're under arrest on suspicion
of multiple drug cases. damn it!
- Stop resisting.
- Grab your weapons.
Hey!
You bastard.
Kill him!
Assaulting the police is a crime!
Get him. Kill him.
Hey! What are you doing?
Help me!
You are surrounded by the police!
Drop all weapons now!
Hold still!
Don't move!
Come down!
Get down here!
Are you okay?
Wounds are just a mark of honor.
Our superior's followed
these drug traffickers for a long time.
- All thanks to you.
- You did great. too.
Don't mention it.
Gotta get back to work now.
Go!
Hey.
You take the lead now.
Drug trafficker.
Piss here for your whole life.
Go away.
Watch out.
I know you're not used to prison life.
Try to rest as much as you can.
Otherwise. you won't be able to hold on.
I am fine.
I can take care of myself.
How about you?
It's been so hot lately.
Will you use the fan?
Instead of saving on electricity?
Tell me.
Don't worry about me.
When did I worry about you?
I'm just asking you a few questions.
You should go back to Shanghai
and find Uncle Bong.
- Take a break.
- I could go any time.
We can go together after you are released.
It might be a long wait.
Good conduct. be granted remission…
You'll be released soon.
It's not just a few years.
What?
Do you remember what Lawyer Li said?
Pleading guilty can reduce your sentence.
- Plus. you're a first-time offender.
- Someone in my cell
got an eight-year sentence
for trafficking 200 grams of drugs.
In my case.
it's one kilogram.
Is it calculated this way?
When I get out.
will you still be around?
I talked to a legal aid lawyer.
He said Kit's case can be won.
He's preparing to help us
overturn the guilty plea.
As long as you admit it was misleading.
- Kit will be fine.
- We didn't mislead anyone.
You know all the facts clearly.
and there's even a signed confession
from Ma Ka-kit.
You bastards.
You knew that Kit was innocent.
Yet you said we couldn't win
and advised him to plead guilty.
claiming it would reduce the sentence.
With good behavior credits
and deducting the holidays.
he'll be out in around ten years.
- I'm dead by that time!
- What're you doing!
- Call the police.
- No need.
You should go.
Just go.
There was a teenager
wrongly accused of murder.
There were doubts about his case.
The boss said he must be prosecuted.
The police officers said
they wouldn't investigate further.
What did you do?
Those British guys
gave up the investigation.
so I went to find evidence on my own.
In the end. that boy
was acquitted. right?
How did you know?
You've talked about this case
many times.
It happened over 40 years ago.
You solved the case too.
Your boss
even gave you this medal.
I thought this case
happened just five days ago.
Anyway.
law enforcers must stay true
to their mission.
Even if one day you couldn't walk anymore.
you wouldn't have any regrets.
Maybe you just need to stop and rest.
We've been talking for a while.
Do you still remember who I am?
I'm hungry.
Take me back to the retirement home.
Okay.
Why are you so slow?
Back in the day.
your dad…
I saw some thieves robbing
a jewelry store and then got on a bus.
I chased them all the way
from Mong Kok to Tsim Sha Tsui
and finally caught them.
Can you speed up?
Can you handle it?
Of course I can.
Then hold on tight.
Let's go.
Are you okay? Is this fast enough?
AFTER A JEWELRY STORE ROBBERY.
A HEROIC COP CAUGHT THREE ROBBERS
Your Honor.
the first defendant. my client Ma Ka-kit.
has no understanding of the law.
He only pleaded guilty because
he was misled by his former lawyer.
This is extremely unfair.
Therefore. I would like to apply
to overturn the guilty plea.
Any remarks from the prosecution?
I have no remarks. Your Honor.
How could you offer no remarks
when they asked for a reverse plea?
Are you intentionally making way?
We won the case. You intentionally
put us at a disadvantage.
Mr. Fok. I don't understand
what you're doing.
Actually. Ma Ka-kit
has always wanted a reduced sentence.
Admitting guilt was enough. right?
Why do the reverse plea then?
Who would stake a ten-year sentence?
What if he's being misled?
We're just giving him another chance.
The Department of Justice
is responsible for prosecution.
and their main duty
is to convict the accused.
Mr. Fok. now you're helping the defense.
What are you trying to do?
You want to prove his innocence?
That's not how I see it. Mr. Yeung.
I believe that as prosecutors.
we should convict the guilty
and establish
the innocence of the innocent.
After Ma Ka-kit admitted his guilt.
then denied it.
it's clear
that one of them is lying.
or maybe both are lying.
Playing along with him
is a waste of manpower. resources.
and the most precious thing.
time. Mr. Fok.
Okay. Mr. Bao.
I want you to summon
Li Sze-man and Au Pak-man
to testify in court regarding
Ma Ka-kit's lack of honesty.
Okay.
And regarding this case.
I want to assign you
as the lead prosecutor.
Please demonstrate to Mr. Fok
how prosecutors handle cases.
Excuse me.
Lunchtime.
That's all.
Court.
Since this case involves
an on-site arrest.
the prosecution has decided
to continue prosecuting
the first and second defendants.
The prosecution will first
summon Inspector Lee King-wai.
who was responsible
for the arrest operation. to testify.
During the arrest that day.
Ma Ka-kit attempted to escape.
At that time. my client saw
a stranger without uniform.
holding a questionable warrant card.
so he got scared and ran.
How can false documents
be a reasonable excuse?
The whole team deceived him with
false documents. How is that possible?
Ridiculous.
No. Your Honor.
I just want to point out
that my client was terrified at that time.
I have no other questions. Your Honor.
I. Li Sze-man. solemnly. sincerely.
and truly declare and affirm
that the testimony
I give is based solely on the facts.
the whole truth.
and nothing but the truth.
Miss Li Sze-man. as far as you know.
why did Ma Ka-kit plead guilty?
Was he aware of the crime
he was confessing to?
Ma Ka-kit wanted a reduced sentence.
so he pleaded guilty.
All the documents
have his personal signature.
so he was fully aware
of the crime he confessed to.
Ms. Li.
do you admit that you misled
my client into pleading guilty?
My client committed a crime
and wanted a reduced sentence.
I suggest you plead guilty
because pleading guilty now
can reduce your sentence by one-third.
Barrister Li's advice is the best
and the quickest way to get you out.
I was reasonably
doing my best to help him.
This bitch told us we'll definitely lose
if we go to trial.
She misled Kit into confessing.
She is lying in court right now.
Why isn't she being arrested?
Is there no justice?
Uncle. please respect the court.
Otherwise. I have to ask you to leave.
As a judge. you should uphold justice.
- You're covering for her…
- Bailiffs.
Please ask this gentleman
to leave and calm down.
She is lying. yet you don't arrest her.
Is there still law?
Why isn't she being arrested?
-Barrister for the second defendant.
-No rules of law!
You may begin your cross-examination.
Thank you. Your Honor.
Ms. Li.
when the first defendant
pleaded guilty initially.
did he clearly and explicitly state
that he did not lend
his address to my client.
the second defendant. Chan Kwok-wing?
The testimony clearly states
he didn't lend his address to anyone.
In other words.
this case concerns the criminal acts
of the first defendant.
My client has been innocent all along.
Do you agree?
You can say that.
Mr. Au Pak-man.
as the assistant
of the former defense lawyer.
you have been involved
in this case. Can you describe
your relationship
with the first defendant?
All our conversations
are built on mutual trust.
You could also say
our relationship is good.
Your Honor. I have no further questions.
I do.
Prosecutor.
Would you like to conduct
a second cross-examination?
Yes. Your Honor.
Mr. Au Pak-man.
The first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
said that you
and Lawyer Li Sze-man misled him.
- Why did he say that?
- Perhaps due to his lack of education.
he is easily influenced by others.
And he is quite naive.
easily swayed by others' words.
Are you taking advantage of his naivety
by asking him to plead guilty?
Prosecutor.
Do you know what you are doing?
You're shooting yourself in the foot.
This is not a playground.
Your Honor. please do not misunderstand.
I must first understand
the character of the first defendant
in order to assess the credibility
of the testimony he provided.
Then. please pay attention to the logic
of your questioning. all right?
Very well. Let me ask differently.
Mr. Au.
Are you providing free defense
for the first defendant?
Yes.
Our law firm
has been handling pro bono cases.
Pro bono cases means you
provide free defense for individuals.
Normally. you first confirm
whether the client
is guilty or not
before helping them. am I right?
I disagree with you.
Even if Ma Ka-kit is truly guilty.
I would still intercede for him.
So. you told him to plead guilty.
In my opinion.
all young people are inherently good.
Even if Ma Ka-kit is guilty.
he should be given a chance.
So. if the court
were to find him guilty today.
I would hope for a lenient sentence.
Objection.
I object to the witness
implying my client's guilt.
What are you objecting to?
He is advocating for leniency
for your client.
Objection overruled.
Your Honor.
allow me to finish my questions.
Mr. Au. let me ask you again.
Did you advise the first defendant
to admit to a crime he didn't commit?
I don't know how to answer
such a leading question.
Witness doesn't need to answer.
Prosecutor. are you shooting
yourself in the foot again?
What are you doing?
With all due respect. Your Honor.
I'm just suggesting
you consider it carefully.
So does the jury
and everyone in the court.
If the first defendant can receive
a reduced sentence by pleading guilty.
which he did. the case was settled.
Why would he overturn
his own testimony and guilty plea?
There is no logic.
Therefore. I have reason
to question the evidence
provided by the two witnesses.
Prosecutor.
are you trying to turn
your witnesses into hostile witnesses?
Your Honor.
I just want to fairly. impartially.
and objectively assist the court
and to find the truth.
I have no more questions.
Mr. Au.
When the first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
initially pleaded guilty.
did he submit three mitigation letters?
Yes.
We did submit
those documents to the court.
hoping they would consider
a sentence reduction.
All letters have been filed in court.
You can read them carefully.
The first letter was written by
an executive director of a listed company.
Mr. Au. have you ever considered.
or had doubts about.
under what circumstances
the first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
would know. or when did he know.
or have the opportunity to know.
an executive director of a listed company?
As his legal team.
even if we have doubts.
we must believe our client.
Understood.
The second letter
was written by a social worker.
stating that Ma Ka-kit had often
participated in volunteer activities.
However. upon further investigation.
the NGO stated
that they never organized the activities
mentioned in the letter.
What are your thoughts. Mr. Au?
I think it's inappropriate
for me to comment.
Your Honor.
I believe you should not allow
the defense lawyer to continue
questioning regarding the letter
as it's irrelevant to the case.
I agree. Your Honor.
Sit down.
Mr. Ho. please continue.
Thank you. Your Honor.
Ma Ka-kit
claimed that his former boss
wrote the final letter.
It states that he is
a diligent and honest person.
The letter mentions that his employment
started in December 2019.
but that company had already
been liquidated in 2017.
So. this letter was actually
forged by Ma Ka-kit.
All the letters were arranged by them.
- It has nothing to do with me!
- Your Honor.
I would like
to respectfully reply regarding
what the defense lawyer just said.
The defense lawyer hastily
attacked the first defendant
before the authenticity
of these three letters were verified.
Could he be intentionally damaging
the integrity of the first defendant?
- Objection. Your Honor.
- Your Honor…
Your Honor. I object.
I request a 15-minute recess.
I didn't do anything.
Your Honor. I also want to remind you.
If these three letters
could possibly have been forged.
they cannot be used as evidence.
Prosecutor Fok. what exactly do you want?
Defense is my responsibility. not yours.
Mr. Cheng. you claimed your client
was misled by someone.
It's all talk.
Do you have any evidence?
I have no evidence
to prove that he was misled.
but there is also no evidence
to prove that he wasn't misled.
- Mr. Cheng. my learned friend.
- Benefit of the doubt…
My learned friend.
Could you please be more professional?
You should help your client find evidence.
If you can't find any evidence.
find witnesses.
You are useless.
Why babble?
How are you even a defence lawyer?
Mr. Bao.
This prosecutor of yours
is constantly asking questions
beneficial to the defendant.
This is completely illogical.
And he's openly insulting
the opposing lawyer in court.
Totally ridiculous.
If you can't control your people.
I will sue you for contempt of court.
Your Honor.
Mr. Fok is not being contemptuous.
He's just employing
a creative questioning approach.
Your Honor. it has nothing
to do with Prosecutor Bao.
I hope you can carefully examine
whether Ma Ka-kit was truly misled or not.
Mr Fok.
When I was in your position.
you were still wearing diapers.
I will remind you
that you are in no position
to teach me how to see clearly.
On the contrary. I should be
teaching you how to see clearly.
As the prosecutor. defending the defendant
is not your responsibility.
So. come back.
Your Honor. I apologize.
but I would like to kindly remind you
that our duty in criminal prosecution
is not solely to ensure
the defendant's conviction
but to present credible evidence
of the crimes
we are presenting to the jury.
Are you teaching me
how to do my job again?
Should I take off my robe
and give it to you to wear?
Or give you my judge's wig?
Your Honor. what I mean is that
you have already influenced the jury's
perception of the first defendant.
So. I request that you
dismiss the jury immediately
and order a retrial.
Court is adjourned.
Court.
I'm at a loss for words.
Have some coffee.
Thanks.
You need to assess the situation.
It's like a police baton.
Only extend when necessary
and retract when unnecessary.
If you extend it all the time.
you'll suffer.
I will watch your trial at 3:30.
Shouldn't you stay for the verdict?
Watch or not. nothing will change.
We need to remember that
there must be a majority consensus
for a ruling to be valid.
It can be 7-0. 6-1. or 5-2.
If it's 4-3. there'll be a retrial.
Mr. Fok.
The courtroom is truly a strange place.
A bunch of legal professionals
struggling with each other.
leaving it to seven laymen
to determine someone's fate.
But you did well just now.
Don't worry about the outcome.
We all have the same goal.
and that is to help Kit.
Mr. Au. cut the bullshit.
Chief Juror.
- Have you reached a verdict?
- Yes.
Is the verdict unanimous?
No.
Is it a majority verdict?
Yes.
What was the vote result?
5-2.
Is the first defendant
guilty or not guilty?
Guilty.
Is the second defendant
guilty or not guilty?
Not guilty.
You are helping Chan Kwok-wing all along.
You pushed Ma Ka-kit into hell.
didn't you?
I will now pronounce the verdict.
The first defendant. Ma Ka-kit.
is guilty of drug trafficking.
Due to his lack of remorse
and the waste of court resources.
he must be severely punished.
He is sentenced to 27 years in prison.
The second defendant. Chan Kwok-wing.
is acquitted and released.
- Court is adjourned.
- Court.
Kit.
Stay strong.
Don't worry.
Grandpa won't let you
sit in prison for 27 years.
I wouldn't be alive to see you released.
Don't worry.
I'll find a way.
Sorry.
Trust me. I will help you.
I'll be in prison for 27 years.
How will you help me?
- Mr. Au. good morning.
- Morning.
Madam Cheung.
- Hi.
- Debbie.
Hello. Man.
Let me introduce you.
Barrister Li.
She specializes in commercial fraud cases.
She can help you.
You can count on me.
- KC.
- You're back?
Let me go first.
I've taken on another civil case.
It's a piece of cake for you.
Last time. you mentioned
wanting a diamond over ten carats.
I found a good one for you in Belgium.
Flawless.
Do you know what brought the client to us?
It's their helplessness.
Just like sick people
going to see a doctor.
Guilty ones going
to church for confession.
or having a villain hitting ritual.
It's all the same.
But you're different
because you understand the law.
You're their savior.
It's all thanks to your selfless efforts.
working tirelessly at night.
that the Department of Justice
can uphold the rule of law for society.
But there are still
many crises and challenges.
I hope everyone sticks to their posts
and continues to uphold
justice for our citizens.
Bao. thank you for taking care
of our colleagues.
You're welcome. Director.
- This is Fok Chi-ho.
- Hello. Director.
Welcome
to the Department of Justice family.
During your time in the police force.
you were renowned
for fearlessly catching criminals
and working diligently.
We believe that with your experience
as a police officer.
you can provide us
with a different perspective.
Mr. Yeung here is the most experienced.
If you have any questions.
he can guide you appropriately.
You should work together closely.
Absolutely. I hope so.
I will do my best to assist Mr. Fok.
He's smart. Everything will be fine.
Rest assured. Director.
I understand
that Prosecutor Fok
still has doubts about your first case.
But as the prosecution.
even if we see a problem.
only the defense has the right to appeal.
At this stage. there's not much
the Department of Justice can do.
I see. Director.
However. it's just a hypothesis.
let's say the defendant
requests an appeal.
I really hope that you. as Director.
will examine this case.
Mr. Fok. why are you so eager
for the defendant to file an appeal?
The court has already
made a clear judgment.
I really want to know what the problem is.
Or do you simply want to see
the DOJ lose a lawsuit?
This kind of rational discussion
is part of your daily work.
You can revisit it another day.
But today. there's a crucial task
for us to complete.
- Hello. George.
- Hi. Selina.
- Selina.
- It's been a while.
Do you remember? Next month.
our alumni association
is holding a golf tournament.
You're on my team.
Make sure you come early
for the photo shoot.
Alright.
Everyone. come over here.
- Full house today.
- Yes.
- Please have a seat.
- Grand Judge.
- Take a seat.
- Mr. Yeung.
- Grand Judge.
- Mr. Bao.
- Have a seat.
Take a seat.
Director. your subordinate
also calls me "Grand Judge".
He doesn't know
everyone present here
can call me "Grand Judge".
except for you.
Right. Mr. Yeung?
Before 1997.
all judges of the High Court and above
were called "Grand Judge".
That's why they called me that.
After 1997. they unified the title
to "Judge". without the"Grand".
So.
any friends I knew before 1997
can still call me "Grand Judge".
But as for you.
it's not suitable. right?
Thank you for going easy on him.
I should thank you.
Marco. pour the wine.
Mr. Fok.
Frankly.
as a judge. I only consider three rules.
There's no fourth.
It's witnesses. physical evidence.
and the jury's decision.
Listen.
Honestly.
sometimes. one can't
always do as one like.
I know the defendant is guilty.
but if there's no evidence.
I have to let them go.
Conversely.
sometimes I know they're innocent.
but if there's evidence.
I have to convict them.
These are traditional rules.
Inevitably. even as a "Grand Judge".
I still have to follow the rules.
There's no reason for you to ignore them
and do as you please. right?
But this time. I understand.
It's your first time working
for the Department of Justice.
and you have no experience.
I'll forgive you this time.
Okay.
Cut the chatter. Let's drink.
This bottle of wine is extraordinary.
Parker gave it a score of 100.
It's a 1992 Chateau Leblanc.
Let's all try it.
I bought it at an auction in France.
In 1982. this lady was abandoned
by her husband and got divorced.
While stomping grapes and making wine.
she cried the whole time.
Her tears fell into the grape juice.
So. now. when you drink it.
there's a taste of her sorrow.
Let's all drink.
See if there's any taste of sadness.
Mr. Fok. can you taste the sadness?
This bottle of wine is expensive.
Even a glass costs thousands.
Yes.
It's the monthly income
of a poor family in Hong Kong.
Indeed. that's quite sad.
I like your sense of humor.
You're a smart guy.
Uncle Ma.
You sent my grandson to prison.
- What do you want?
- I understand how you feel.
Can you give me a few minutes?
I want to say something.
There are many loopholes in this case.
So. on behalf
of the Department of Justice.
I apologize to you.
Additionally. I want to remind you
that as a citizen. you have the right
to exercise your civil rights
- and file an appeal.
- I don't need your reminder.
I already applied.
Lawyer Cheng told me
not to talk to anyone during this time.
- Okay.
- Stop bothering me.
I want you to believe
- our society is lawful.
- Everyone pretends to be nice.
I don't believe any of your nonsense.
I don't believe you hypocrites.
You're pretending to be the good guys.
Help! Help!
Help!
We've recorded Uncle Ma's statement.
Right after he filed his appeal.
he was attacked.
It was most likely
that paralegal and the lawyer.
We recently seized several
vehicles transporting drugs.
and your case is also
related to drug trafficking.
Be careful.
You really don't have to drive me home.
I can get home myself.
No worries. It's on my way.
It's messy here. Be careful.
Don't mind my humble abode.
Take a seat.
I'll open the window for fresh air.
I'll get you a cup of tea.
Damn.
It ran off again.
- Please have some tea.
- Thanks.
Whenever it rains outside.
it leaks here.
As the saying goes.
"Water is wealth." right?
It's fine. as long
as I won't starve to death.
Did your grandson draw all of these?
Yes. Kit drew them.
He loves drawing tall buildings.
He often tells me that he wants me
to live in a better place.
As soon as he turned 18.
he applied for public housing.
We were hoping to move
to public housing in a few years.
Uncle Ma.
How do you know Li Sze-man?
I was introduced by the owner
of the restaurant where Kit works.
I think his last name is Lau.
He knew Kit was hardworking.
so he referred a paralegal to him.
Then the paralegal introduced us
to the bitch who offered to help for free.
We're too poor to have a choice.
Just talking to a lawyer costs thousands.
How could I afford it?
You legal aid or DOJ folks.
all from the government. can't help us.
After all this chaos. you must be hungry.
Make yourself at home.
I'll make two bowls of noodles.
I didn't realize I was hungry
until you mentioned it.
Just a second.
Mr. Fok. everyone has left already.
Come. Let's have a drink
during Happy Hour.
I found new clues in the Ma Ka-kit case.
You realize
that there's no overtime. right?
Ma Ka-kit's previous boss. Lau Siu-keung.
is a new lead in this case.
We need to find out
about his relationship
with Li Sze-man and Au Pak-man.
It's the only way to help Ma Ka-kit.
According to our intelligence reports.
in recent years. Lau Siu-keung
opened many restaurants.
wine stores. and nightclubs.
He appears to be a legitimate businessman.
Behind the scenes.
he works with triad leaders.
All his businesses are managed
by Au Pak-man's law firm.
Li Sze-man is really something.
She grew up in an orphanage.
and later. Au Pak-man paid
for her education in the United States.
where she also obtained a law license.
If I were her. I'd fall for him too.
I checked the DOJ internal records.
Au Pak-man got his early release
because Li Sze-man won his case.
LUCKY SIX
12-1/20-1
Please conclude. Bao Ding.
Isn't it obvious?
They're the masterminds.
Au Pak-man is so impressive.
He's been in prison
for assault. extortion. money laundering.
drugs… Almost all crimes.
Yet he still works at a law firm.
That's ridiculous.
We can work this out.
Dealing with the evidence is easy
because he wasn't caught red-handed.
- Yes.
- Au Pak Man.
- Get lost!
- Go jerk yourself!
For money laundering.
I take a 20% cut.
Whether it's 100 million or one billion.
I don't care. 20%. that's how it is.
CSD officers said
he diligently studied law in prison.
After being released. he continued
smuggling and trafficking drugs.
But he won all the cases by himself.
He also knows
many influential figures in prison.
We arrested one of them.
Sang. from Cambodia.
SANG'S RECORDS
IN CORRECTIONAL SERVICES DEPARTMENT
SANG'S FINGERPRINT
Cash out.
Let's go.
Keung.
I am in conflict with the God of the Year.
Some drug cars got busted.
The batch in the coconuts was seized.
We should lay low for a while.
Hold deliveries for now.
No deliveries?
The bosses will definitely throw a fit.
Throw a fit?
Let them. then.
If the goods are seized by the cops.
I would go crazy.
The incident with Uncle Ma
was because of you two. right?
You're so smart.
Nothing escapes you.
It could be either Tung or Sang.
Who else could it be?
That's why I always say.
brutes will be brutes.
They only use violence.
Keung.
You're a smart guy.
civilized.
So. in the future. whatever you do.
don't be as foolish as they are.
- Okay?
- Understood. Boss.
Sang. take a seat.
Have a seat.
Your underling
stole my batch of coconuts.
causing me a loss of 50 million.
When will you compensate me?
You can only accuse him of stealing
if he's taken it for himself.
The police confiscated everything.
I want to compensate you.
but Man can't make any deliveries now.
Let's see what he has to say.
Personally. I think
if we make deliveries now.
it's like delivering to the cops.
The 50 million you lost.
I'll personally pay it back.
As for Tung.
I'll give you 30% off
on the next three batches.
- This way. everyone's satisfied.
- A wonderful deal.
You really think that money is everything?
Sang.
I know what you want.
Let me go.
Tung. You're not
going to do this. are you?
I've followed you since I was a kid.
You'll do this to me?
Let me go!
You're crazy.
This time. my underling made a mistake.
I know what to do.
Man.
Give me a hand.
Will you do it or not?
Didn't you hear the boss. dumb-ass?
Hit him.
- Hit him.
- Do it!
Come on.
Sang. I didn't know the cocaine
in those coconuts belonged to you.
Please. give me a chance.
Tung. I know I was wrong.
Please help me plead with Sang.
I beg you…
Don't do this.
Wow. Do you really have to go this far?
Are you satisfied?
I never said I wasn't satisfied.
Take him to a doctor.
Make sure the goods reach us tomorrow.
Bosses…
It's not that I don't want to deliver.
I'm still involved in a case.
I'm being watched closely.
I'll handle your case.
Make sure you keep delivering.
You hear me?
Go.
I'm leaving now. Sang.
You bastard.
You're so brutal.
even with your own underlings.
That's how we do things.
If we don't scare him a little.
he won't deliver the goods.
Hello. Bao Ding.
I can't hear you.
It's noisy. Speak up.
You piece of shit.
You know it's my place. yet you do drugs?
Is your place more important than me?
Without me. you'd have died long ago.
Get the fuck out.
Now! Get out!
Stop playing big brother. you bastard.
I am your big brother. So what?
My last name is Chan.
- Your dad isn't my dad.
- But we share the same mom. don't we?
- Yes. so what?
- Get lost.
I'll leave once I've had enough.
- Stop!
- Bitch!
- Someone's here.
- Someone is filming us.
I've seen him in court.
Sorry.
What are you filming?
Give me your phone.
Hey! What's going on? Gang fight. huh?
I called the cops.
Took you long enough. Let's go.
I got what we need. Let's go.
Are you okay?
Go find Wai now.
He's on his way.
Calling the cops?
I'll beat them all too.
- Have you ever been in a fight?
- Never. I was a model student.
Get them!
Hey. Wai? What's taking you so long?
Your friend's fighting
with a whole damn army.
No. I mean he's being beaten up
by a whole damn army.
Don't hit me!
Mr. Fok?
Mr. Fok. it's me.
It's me.
You're lucky to be alive.
- I'll buy you dinner.
- Turns out Lau Siu-keung
is Chan Kwok-wing's half-brother.
I recorded everything.
This place belongs to Lau Siu-keung.
The guys in suits who attacked you earlier
are the security guards.
Every one of them
insisted on hiring a lawyer
and specifically asked
for Au Pak-man's law firm.
Justice will prevail.
Heaven is on our side.
The brothers are obstructing justice.
Ma Ka Kit's case has a good chance now.
Mr. Yeung.
Hey. Mr. Bao.
Got a second to talk?
I'm rushing to the High Court.
- What's the matter?
- It's urgent.
AU PAK-MAN. 42
How do you know Li Sze-man?
I was introduced by the owner
of the restaurant where Kit works.
I think his last name is Lau.
Uncle Ma said that Lau Siu-keung
introduced Au Pak-man to him.
Turns out Lau Siu-keung
and Chan Kwok-wing
are half-brothers.
They have long colluded
to obstruct justice.
Bao. why are you so enthusiastic?
You even joined their team.
Uncle Ma is now filing
an official statement.
You should go and take a look.
The evidence is real.
Now. the Legal Aid Department
is citing. "Judge misdirected the jury."
It has been remitted for retrial.
scheduled in 28 days.
I really don't understand.
Why are they retrying
such a small case over and over?
I don't want people to think
that the DOJ is unprofessional.
Once the statement is done.
the police will submit
the documents to the DOJ.
The DOJ will then consider
whether to accept it or not.
Of course I know.
But I'm done
with all the doubts between us.
What do you want to say? Spit it out.
The DOJ has prosecuted
Au Pak-man three times.
but he walked free every time.
It was the same prosecutor
all three times.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR: YEUNG DIT-LAP
You were the lead prosecutor.
- How long have you known me?
- Thirty-six years.
Don't you know I deal with thousands
of cases each year? Three cases?
Are you using this to question me?
- Mr Yeung.
- Accusing me over these three cases?
Just this afternoon.
I have 38 cases waiting for me.
If you have evidence
to support your accusations.
then please report me immediately.
Otherwise. don't waste my time
with this nonsense.
PAK-MAN DECLINED CALLS
I want a lawyer.
No matter how many retrials.
the result will be the same.
We won't lose.
I don't care about winning or losing.
What matters
is maintaining the public's trust.
Knowing that we have the ability
to uphold the rule of law.
Legal Aid has arranged for you to give
a statement at the police station.
As long as you expose Lau Siu-keung.
tell them he referred you to the lawyer.
then he's guilty of obstructing justice.
There will be a hope for Kit.
It seems Kit really has a chance.
Thank you.
Not at all. It's my duty.
But you will have to testify in court.
- Stay strong.
- Of course I will.
I hope that after Kit is released.
he can reform and return to his studies.
To grow into someone like you.
a great lawyer.
You're too kind.
Your grandson truly has artistic talent.
- I know. right?
- He draws very well.
Nowadays. paintings are pricey.
Actually.
it doesn't matter what he studies.
What matters most is getting a girlfriend.
Seeing him build a family of his own.
That's all I hope for.
I look forward to his wedding.
Of course I'll invite you.
Let me use the restroom.
You can sit at the host's table.
As long as I get to eat.
I beg you. Prosecutor Fok.
You work for the DOJ. right?
Can you talk to the judge
to release me for one day? Just one day.
After that. even a lifetime
in jail wouldn't matter.
I want revenge.
I don't understand.
I really…
Why won't anyone help me?
I really didn't do anything.
I lent my address
just to make a few thousand
to help my grandpa with living expenses.
I simply wished
that we could have better meals.
eat together at a nice table.
and have a home that doesn't leak.
That's it.
Did I really do something wrong?
Ma Ka-kit's relative recently died…
- Now. people are very worried…
- Is it related to the case…
Everyone is paying
close attention to this case.
Is someone trying to silence a witness?
Did the Department of Justice
accuse the wrong person?
Everyone is paying
close attention to this case.
How do you feel about handling this case?
This case has entered
the judicial process.
I should not comment here. Sorry.
If the appeal is successful. would it
damage the reputation of the DOJ?
The DOJ's image
doesn't matter to the rest of the world.
The DOJ works based on evidence.
We present the evidence to the court.
The court makes the final decision.
Here.
Okay.
- Check again.
- Okay.
We've checked this matter many times.
No leads.
No witnesses. no fingerprints.
no murder weapon.
Lots of stores across the street.
Have you checked their CCTV?
Have you checked for any
nearby cars and pedestrians?
Not finding anything
means you haven't done your best.
All of us have been grinding
for 48 hours straight.
You believe we don't want to help?
No evidence and no witnesses.
What can we do?
If there's no way. then find one.
I trust you.
but you need to trust yourself too.
Do you remember what we used to say?
- Stick to our post...
- Stick to our post?
Everyone here
is staying firm at their post!
But we still couldn't solve it.
Even the police are helpless sometimes.
It's not like we can investigate
however we want.
Now I understand
why you gave up back then.
Mr. Fok.
Hi. madam. Long time no see.
Is this your son?
Yes.
- His name is Luke.
- Hello. Uncle.
Hello. Luke.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Still in the Emergency Unit?
Yes. I just finished my board interview.
There's a chance for a promotion.
Great. Keep it up.
- Stick to your post and fight crime.
Officer Fok.
Actually. I was three months pregnant
during that operation seven years ago.
If you didn't save me.
he wouldn't be sitting here.
Thank you.
I never gave up.
I'm just getting old.
I can't be on the front line
my whole life. so I really need your help.
That's why
I transferred
to the Department of Justice.
To defend the last line
of the rule of law.
As long as you have faith.
you can do it.
Stay true to your mission.
It would be great
if everyone had your enthusiasm.
You have it too.
Understand.
Alright. Let's keep going.
Keep going. everyone!
Copy that.
Gotta go.
Bao Ding.
Work's over. You're not leaving?
If you're not with us. then go.
Hey.
There are still over a dozen cases.
We can't finish them before the trial.
You should have stayed a police officer.
If I hadn't met you.
I wouldn't have to work so hard.
Why the sudden transfer to the DOJ?
I have no idea why you did this.
Do you want to know why?
Tell me. Stop being mysterious.
Because I think our work
is a beacon that never fades.
It shines the glory
of fairness and justice
into the hearts of the people.
into every dark corner.
I'm getting old.
I can't catch thieves anymore.
My knees aren't working well.
That's not my issue. I'm still young.
You are right.
Remember your first case. the bet we made?
There was a third person at the scene.
It's a conspiracy to murder.
A bet's a bet.
I'm good at reviewing documents.
Let me help.
There are lots of documents.
Let's go through them together.
I'll take care of this box.
The beacon…
I've extinguished it.
- Fok Sir.
- Okay.
The criminal organization has a pattern.
There are more victims like Ma Ka-kit.
There are many Ma Ka-kits out there.
Before the trial.
we need to find one more Ma Ka-kit
- who is willing to testify.
- Police.
But importing drugs
into Hong Kong by mail…
There are over 300 similar cases per year.
Maybe over 1.000 cases in total.
- We only have a few days.
- I know it's difficult.
but I know you can do it.
A young man went through what you did.
You could help him by appearing in court.
I've done my sentence already.
What do you want?
Go away.
My son just got out
from the juvenile home.
Leave him alone.
I don't mind giving a statement
at the police station.
I'd rather not go to court. though.
I don't want others to know
I've been to prison.
I understand.
but there's a young man just like you.
He also received a parcel
and was accused of drug trafficking.
Stop bothering me.
Was it this person
who introduced you to the lawyer?
He has harmed many people
with the same method.
Please help.
A young man also received a package
and was accused of drug trafficking.
If you testify in court. you can save him.
Everyone. Bingo.
Someone agreed to appear in court.
Well done!
Thank you!
Well done. Mr. Fok.
Hello. Mr. Fok.
You took leave today. so I came over
to check on you.
Is everything alright?
Thank you.
How are things now?
I never thought
the case would get this serious.
Someone even got killed.
When will you be done with this?
Uncle Ma has been killed.
Are you pretending not to know?
His death is a separate case.
A criminal case.
We are the Department of Justice.
Ever thought of becoming a cop again?
Then you can investigate cases
and catch criminals.
You can even become a defense lawyer.
After all. you enjoy being
a defense lawyer.
You're wasting your talents at the DOJ.
Do you know what the DOJ is for?
Let me tell you.
The DOJ is the final gate
of the rule of law.
Now. Uncle Ma
has been murdered.
Ma Ka-kit will be imprisoned for 27 years.
Even if he's guilty.
is 27 years a reasonable sentence?
You tell me.
Honestly.
27 years is a bit excessive.
But we are the DOJ.
Do you know how many
pending cases we have?
If every colleague works the way you do.
the DOJ would be paralyzed. Understand?
Given your current state of mind.
you are no longer suitable to be
the lead prosecutor of this case.
It's even more unsuitable
for you to remain in the DOJ.
I have submitted a letter to the CSB
requesting your transfer.
You will receive notice
in one month. okay?
Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- Get out.
Thank you.
You're a loser.
Cut the act.
- All that education. you're still a loser.
- What?
Wearing a suit doesn't make you classy.
You're the type
who'd just walk past an old lady
falling in the street.
You have no friends. You're selfish.
You only think of yourself.
You don't even own a pet.
Go home and jerk off.
Oh. don't leave just yet.
Here's the evidence
of your collaboration with Au Pak-man.
Stop slandering me!
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you taking off your jacket?
- You want a one-on-one?
- I've put up with you too long.
- Come on!
- Talking about Au Pak-man all the time.
The Treasury pays you
thousands each month.
- You bastard.
- I'm giving you one chance.
- Yeung Dit-lap.
- If you win.
- Let's see how strong you are.
- I'll let you off.
- Let's see what you've got.
- Let's fight!
Come on!
- Fight with me?
- The world is full of people
- like Au.
- Cut the crap.
Can you arrest them all?
Damn you.
Come on.
Let's go.
Beat me and I'll back you up.
Get ready to back me up. then.
Damn. You wish.
So. you're playing tricks on me
with blank papers?
This is the only way to ignite
your determination.
You have to keep your word.
Brother Tung.
here are the US dollars you asked for.
Count it yourself.
Nakamura. put that over there.
Yes. sir.
Gentlemen. the money laundry is done.
If you need anything. call me anytime.
Smart guy.
Man delivered the goods as agreed.
Everybody's happy.
But I still have something
to ask Lau Siu-keung.
- Hey.
- Yes. Tung?
The police are looking
for evidence against you.
This definitely affects Man too.
You'll bring trouble to us.
It's my fault. I'll settle the matter.
Let's not bring up anything
that ruins the vibe.
We're all so happy now.
Let's just drink.
I've sorted it out with Keung already.
He will turn himself in and plead guilty.
Then the whole matter will be resolved.
In any case. it won't bother you.
Come on. Let's drink.
Here.
Thank you. Sang.
Gentlemen…
Keung is very capable.
If there's any offense.
please forgive him.
For my sake. don't blame him.
Today
is Sang's birthday.
I prepared
a small birthday present for you.
See if you like it.
Man…
- Such a smart guy.
- Sang…
I wish you dazzling charm.
Like fireworks. Charming forever.
Time's up.
Have you gone crazy?
Today is my birthday.
We agreed I would shoot.
Yes. it's your birthday.
but we agreed to shoot at 12:30.
- You shot the old guy. It's my turn now.
- If you wanted to shoot.
you should have done it
at the stern of the ship.
You made a mess.
Now I need to replace the furniture.
It takes time to order it from Italy.
I couldn't wait.
What if he drank all my booze?
Let's drink.
Happy Birthday.
The body in the sea this morning
has been confirmed as Lau Siu-keung.
Even with the testimony
from the laundry shop girl.
we still lack of evidence to charge him.
Their next target will be Chan Kwok-wing.
We don't know if he's hiding
or has already been killed.
We can't find him.
The trial is about to begin.
We need to find Chan Kwok-wing ASAP.
As long as you tell the truth.
we will help you shorten your sentence.
And if your testimony can help
incriminate the whole gang
of drug traffickers.
I will also consider helping you
apply for amnesty.
Being a tainted witness
is in your best interest.
Your sentence reduction
depends on how much you say.
I have evidence about Lau Siu-keung
that can prove
that Au Pak-man is the culprit.
I even know where his drug den is.
I want a shortened sentence.
Do you have any other choices?
Prosecutor Yeung.
Fok Chi-ho isn't here.
Just do what I say later.
My leg…
I can't walk.
Help me.
- Sit down.
- Help me.
- Can you still walk?
- Take him with you.
Court is in session. Get going.
- Go.
- Enough? Sir?
Help me. Officer.
- Take care.
- Call the police.
Just call the cops.
Don't let me die.
Quickly. call the cops.
I'm Inspector Lee King-wai.
I'm at the intersection of Ki Lung Street…
Hey.
Help me.
Don't let me die.
Hey. Help me.
Defendant Ma Ka-kit's appeal
in the drug trafficking
conspiracy case was successful.
The case will be retried today.
Miss Cheung Yeuk-sum.
A few years ago.
you received a parcel at your home.
Inside. there were 500 grams of cocaine.
and at that time.
you admitted to drug trafficking.
Is that true?
Actually. it was Chan Kwok-wing.
He gave me HK$1000 to use my home address.
I didn't know there were drugs
in that parcel.
My former boss. Lau Siu-keung.
introduced me to Au Pak-man.
They were the ones
who told me to plead guilty.
Do you have evidence?
I've been jailed for this.
That's evidence!
The key figures in our case.
Chan Kwok-wing and Lau Siu-keung.
are not present in the courtroom.
So. I would like to summon
the next witness.
Mr. Au Pak-man. to testify
and help reconstruct
the sequence of events.
This case was actually easy for me
to handle within the law.
You bastards insisted on killing.
You killed the older one.
but let the little one walk.
If Chan Kwok-wing
has any evidence. I'm screwed.
If you run away.
this case will never be closed.
Sooner or later. the police
will find out more and more.
Eventually. we'll both be doomed.
Settle it in court tomorrow.
and we'll all be happy.
Are you crazy?
Are you forcing me to appear in court?
You've got to be kidding me.
If I go down. you're going with me.
Use your damn brain.
How much have you earned
over the years. thanks to me?
Without me. you're nothing but shit.
I'm screwed. It's just a matter of time.
Stay calm.
Let's fix this together.
I've arranged it all. Do you know?
Where on Earth
does the sunrise appear first?
It's Fiji.
I already bought a small island there.
I'm ready to go and enjoy my life.
In Hong Kong.
there are skyscrapers everywhere.
It's hard to see the sunrise anymore.
In Chan Kwok-wing's testimony.
he also indicated
that he and his brother.
Lau Siu-keung. were working for you.
He was primarily responsible
for borrowing others' addresses
and receiving parcels.
His brother was responsible
for introducing lawyers to the victims.
including Miss Cheung Yeuk-sum
and Mr. Ma Ka-kit.
What's your explanation
for these accusations?
Listen to me.
Go to court tomorrow
and resolve the matter.
KUEN HANG CLUB
I'll take you with me to Fiji.
Once we're there.
you'll be able to see
the sunrise every day.
I'll take care of things
outside of the courtroom.
First of all.
I don't know what statement
he gave to the police.
But one thing I do know is that
his claims are meaningless.
unless he shows up in court to testify.
Prosecutor Yeung.
I know exactly what you're planning.
You're using my courtroom
to try and expose the crimes of others.
What are you trying to achieve in the end?
To answer your question. Your Honor.
I want to request
that Chan Kwok-wing testifies in court
as a special witness for the prosecution.
He didn't submit a request.
Without a request. I won't approve it.
- It is unfair to the defense.
- Your Honor.
I'm fine with it.
Are you two messing with me?
Your Honor.
I humbly request your approval
for Chan Kwok-wing to testify in court.
If you're not satisfied
after hearing his testimony.
I'm willing to bear
the consequences and responsibilities.
When will your witness appear. then?
Please stand back from the train doors.
Officer Fok.
Prosecutor Fok.
Sang and I spent ten years
hiding in Cambodia all because of you.
You've arrested so many people.
Of course. you can't recognize me.
That stubborn old man. Uncle Ma.
I stabbed him a dozen times.
His guts spilled all over the floor.
I really enjoyed it. It's your turn now.
This is how the law works. Prosecutor Fok.
Hey.
Objection.
Would you like to appeal?
The courtroom is a place
to uncover the truth.
Time means nothing
in the face of the truth.
So. no matter how much time it takes.
we must wait for the truth to come out.
Right?
Prosecutor Yeung. could you
please stop reciting poetry here?
When can he come?
Sorry. Your Honor…
There was some traffic.
My brother left evidence for me.
It includes account books.
drug trade records. and…
Au Pak-man's bank accounts.
He told me to disclose everything
to protect myself.
Ma Ka-kit didn't know
the parcel contained drugs.
Au Pak-man told me to plead guilty.
He said if I didn't. he would kill me.
Do you think this scares me?
Even if I have to go to prison.
I'll expose you.
Au Pak-man. you bastard.
Prosecutor. do you have
any further statements?
Ladies and gentlemen.
In Hong Kong.
the court values evidence above all.
However. sometimes
evidence does not guarantee
truth or justice.
Furthermore.
no judicial system is completely perfect.
Sometimes. loopholes may even appear.
These loopholes
are often exploited
by individuals with malicious intent.
It causes innocent people to suffer.
Just like the ongoing Ma Ka-kit case.
Just one wrongful judgment
can destroy an entire family.
That's why we. the judicial personnel.
will not allow any miscarriage of justice
under our watch.
We won't allow
miscarriages of justice on Ma Ka-kit.
We won't allow that
to happen to anyone.
This is our conscience
as legal personnel. Your Honor.
This court hereby pronounces the verdict.
The first defendant. Ma Ka-kit. is found
not guilty of drug trafficking charges
and is acquitted and released.
The DOJ celebrates the fact
that the Ma Ka-kit case
has been successfully appealed.
The DOJ will continue to optimize
their performance.
enhancing the efficiency. quality.
and consistency of prosecution.
We'll also strengthen our cooperation
with other government departments
to provide high-quality legal services
to Hong Kong society.
ensuring fairness and justice
in the judicial process.
AU PAK-MAN
You overturned your verdict
in the Ma Ka-kit case.
Does this suggest
that the justice system lacks fairness?
Could this have been
the result of human error?
That's right.
I admit
that the initial judgment
in this case
was indeed flawed.
This has raised doubts
and concerns among the public.
Regarding this matter.
I sincerely
regret and apologize.
QUALIFIED YOUTH PROGRAM TUITION
ASSISTANCE APPLICATION NOTICE
FOK CHI-HO
Now. the case
has finally come to a clear conclusion.
The truth is revealed.
The most important thing
is that justice is done.
That's most important.
Court.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today